http://www.lydbury.co.uk/privacy-policy.html

Go to content
Privacy Policy This privacy policy explains how the data you input to this site will be held, what it will be used for and the data protection policy of Lydbury English Centre Ltd. If you have any requests concerning personal information please contact us via our contact page.We are committed to protecting your personal information and will keep the information you entrust safely and securely. Lydbury English Centre Ltd which is registered under the Data Protection Act and will comply with that Act’s provisions.We collect personal information from you through the use of product enquiry and registration forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We process personal information collected via the GE Website in order to:Provide you with information about out products and servicesConduct specific marketing campaignsAssist us in meeting customer expectations in evolving new productsWe may also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. This information includes demographic data and browsing patterns. Any information of this kind is used in aggregate form only and none of the data includes any information that would enable you or any other individual to be identified. We use information in aggregate form to:Monitor usage of the siteReview product demand and as an aid to future developmentTo access marketing profilesWe employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, including fulfilling subscription orders, sending e-mails and postal mail, and analysing data. We will ensure that these companies only use such information under our direction to perform these functions, and that they have adequate procedures in place to deal with your data securely.If we transfer your data to these companies we will ensure that they process your data in accordance with this privacy policy and the Data Protection Act.We have reviewed our handling of financial data under the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard Guidlines and confirm that we do not retain any client financial information be it electronic or manual. All credit and debit card transactions, whether on-line or by virtual terminal, are conducted via a secure internet environment provided by Small Green Tree Ltd and/or PayPal and private client information is not retained by Lydbury English Centre Ltd or any agent acting on our behalf.We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. Should The Lydbury English Centre Ltd's privacy policy change the latest changes will be found here on our website.Cookie Policy
Back to content
